[
    {
        "front": "Dama ",
        "back": "(Suffix for Coin/s)",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Satsu",
        "back": "(Suddix for Note/s)",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Ikura",
        "back": "How much",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaban",
        "back": "Bag",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Baiku",
        "back": "Bike",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuruma",
        "back": "Car",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Keitai Denwa, Sumahon",
        "back": "Cell Phone, Smart Phone",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Pasokon",
        "back": "Laptop, Computer",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Tokei",
        "back": "Watch/Clock",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Ude Tokei",
        "back": "Wrist Watch",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Isu",
        "back": "Chair",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Tsukue",
        "back": "Table",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Ie",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Pen",
        "back": "Pen",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Kutsu",
        "back": "Shoes",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Chotto",
        "back": "Little bit",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Totemo",
        "back": "Very",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Doru",
        "back": "Dollar",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Yasumi",
        "back": "Holiday, Break",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyūjitsu",
        "back": "National Holiday",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Kyukei",
        "back": "Break",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Natsu Yasumi",
        "back": "Summer Break",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Gakkō ",
        "back": "School",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaban",
        "back": "Bag",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Pasokon",
        "back": "Computer",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Ocha",
        "back": "(Green) Tea",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Osake",
        "back": "Alcohol",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Shigoto",
        "back": "Work/Job",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Seki",
        "back": "Seat",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Shimbun",
        "back": "Newspaper",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Biru ",
        "back": "Building",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Biiru",
        "back": "Bear",
        "chapter": 2
    },
    {
        "front": "Shukudai",
        "back": "Homework",
        "chapter": 2
    }
]